#5.7 Monte Carlo method for computing integrals

#suppose we have a beta(14.26, 23.19)
#we want to estimate a function of a parameter say p^2
#we want mean and se of p^2

#generate sample

p=rbeta(1000, 14.26, 23.19)
est=mean(p^2)
se=sd(p^2)/sqrt(1000)
c(est, se)

#when posterior distribution is in familiar form, we can get samples directly
#then we can do Monte Carlo estimates for posterior means
#for any function of the paremeters of interest (see 5.8 intro)





